<resources>
    <string name="app_name">二刺猿</string>
    <string name="_null"/>
    <string name="_n">\n</string>
    <string name="explain_test">
        爆裂吧现实，粉碎吧精神，放逐这个世界，遵从血之盟约，吾在此召唤汝，夜之女王！\n\n
        立誓今生尊你为王，用我热血为你封疆。\n\n
        无论是现今还是以前我所保护的都是一样，从来就没有变过啊!!!\n\n
        隐约雷鸣 阴霾天空 即使天无雨 我亦留此地。\n\n
        尽管岁月浮光世事喧嚣，心中却始终有一个关于你的童话：无论你在哪里，我都会径直奔向你，送你一世不会凋谢的樱花。\n\n
        谁都不可能和谁在一起一辈子。人就是这样，必须去习惯失去。\n\n
        如果生命能够重来，无论几次我都要到你身边，我已经别无所求，已经没有什么比你更重要。\n\n
        我想这世间一定有一个人，和我一起努力着，做着类似的事情，怀揣着同样的梦想，然后某天，不期而遇。\n\n
        在梦中，我以为人生很漫长，会远得连尽头也看不见，没想到我匆匆翻看，人生，却再也无法逆转。在当下，我以为时间很重，会重得连时针都走不动。没想到我轻轻一吹，时间，却再也没回来过。\n\n
        遇见竟然需要如此用力，穿越错位的时空，仰望陨落的星辰，你没留下你的名字，我却无法忘记你写在我手心的名字——我爱你。\n\n
        回望当初，那时我一定也一直在训练自己迈步，如果有一天，能够走得更稳更远了，就去见她吧。\n\n
        时间带着鲜明的恶意，缓缓地从我的身上流过，我只好咬紧牙关，拼命地不让眼泪落下来。\n\n
    </string>

    <!--<string name="url_img_home_banner">https://b-ssl.duitang.com/uploads/item/201801/08/20180108181057_VSyJF.gif</string>-->
    <!--http://img2.100bt.com/upload/ttq/20140606/1402032172085.gif-->
    <string name="url_img_home_movie">https://cdn.dribbble.com/users/1361661/screenshots/6743663/little_dragon_maiden_2x.png</string>
    <string name="url_img_home_live">https://cdn.dribbble.com/users/1361661/screenshots/6673317/music_girl.png</string>
    <string name="url_img_home_tv">https://cdn.dribbble.com/users/1361661/screenshots/6748203/little_dragon_maiden_____2x.png</string>
    <string name="url_img_home_tools">https://cdn.dribbble.com/users/1361661/screenshots/6816008/_____3___4_________1x.png</string>




    <string name="large_text">
        "Material is the metaphor.\n\n"

        "A material metaphor is the unifying theory of a rationalized space and a system of motion."
        "The material is grounded in tactile reality, inspired by the study of paper and ink, yet "
        "technologically advanced and open to imagination and magic.\n"
        "Surfaces and edges of the material provide visual cues that are grounded in reality. The "
        "use of familiar tactile attributes helps users quickly understand affordances. Yet the "
        "flexibility of the material creates new affordances that supercede those in the physical "
        "world, without breaking the rules of physics.\n"
        "The fundamentals of light, surface, and movement are key to conveying how objects move, "
        "interact, and exist in space and in relation to each other. Realistic lighting shows "
        "seams, divides space, and indicates moving parts.\n\n"

        "Bold, graphic, intentional.\n\n"

        "The foundational elements of print based design typography, grids, space, scale, color, "
        "and use of imagery guide visual treatments. These elements do far more than please the "
        "eye. They create hierarchy, meaning, and focus. Deliberate color choices, edge to edge "
        "imagery, large scale typography, and intentional white space create a bold and graphic "
        "interface that immerse the user in the experience.\n"
        "An emphasis on user actions makes core functionality immediately apparent and provides "
        "waypoints for the user.\n\n"

        "Motion provides meaning.\n\n"

        "Motion respects and reinforces the user as the prime mover. Primary user actions are "
        "inflection points that initiate motion, transforming the whole design.\n"
        "All action takes place in a single environment. Objects are presented to the user without "
        "breaking the continuity of experience even as they transform and reorganize.\n"
        "Motion is meaningful and appropriate, serving to focus attention and maintain continuity. "
        "Feedback is subtle yet clear. Transitions are efﬁcient yet coherent.\n\n"

        "3D world.\n\n"

        "The material environment is a 3D space, which means all objects have x, y, and z "
        "dimensions. The z-axis is perpendicularly aligned to the plane of the display, with the "
        "positive z-axis extending towards the viewer. Every sheet of material occupies a single "
        "position along the z-axis and has a standard 1dp thickness.\n"
        "On the web, the z-axis is used for layering and not for perspective. The 3D world is "
        "emulated by manipulating the y-axis.\n\n"

        "Light and shadow.\n\n"

        "Within the material environment, virtual lights illuminate the scene. Key lights create "
        "directional shadows, while ambient light creates soft shadows from all angles.\n"
        "Shadows in the material environment are cast by these two light sources. In Android "
        "development, shadows occur when light sources are blocked by sheets of material at "
        "various positions along the z-axis. On the web, shadows are depicted by manipulating the "
        "y-axis only. The following example shows the card with a height of 6dp.\n\n"

        "Resting elevation.\n\n"

        "All material objects, regardless of size, have a resting elevation, or default elevation "
        "that does not change. If an object changes elevation, it should return to its resting "
        "elevation as soon as possible.\n\n"

        "Component elevations.\n\n"

        "The resting elevation for a component type is consistent across apps (e.g., FAB elevation "
        "does not vary from 6dp in one app to 16dp in another app).\n"
        "Components may have different resting elevations across platforms, depending on the depth "
        "of the environment (e.g., TV has a greater depth than mobile or desktop).\n\n"

        "Responsive elevation and dynamic elevation offsets.\n\n"

        "Some component types have responsive elevation, meaning they change elevation in response "
        "to user input (e.g., normal, focused, and pressed) or system events. These elevation "
        "changes are consistently implemented using dynamic elevation offsets.\n"
        "Dynamic elevation offsets are the goal elevation that a component moves towards, relative "
        "to the component’s resting state. They ensure that elevation changes are consistent "
        "across actions and component types. For example, all components that lift on press have "
        "the same elevation change relative to their resting elevation.\n"
        "Once the input event is completed or cancelled, the component will return to its resting "
        "elevation.\n\n"

        "Avoiding elevation interference.\n\n"

        "Components with responsive elevations may encounter other components as they move between "
        "their resting elevations and dynamic elevation offsets. Because material cannot pass "
        "through other material, components avoid interfering with one another any number of ways, "
        "whether on a per component basis or using the entire app layout.\n"
        "On a component level, components can move or be removed before they cause interference. "
        "For example, a floating action button (FAB) can disappear or move off screen before a "
        "user picks up a card, or it can move if a snackbar appears.\n"
        "On the layout level, design your app layout to minimize opportunities for interference. "
        "For example, position the FAB to one side of stream of a cards so the FAB won’t interfere "
        "when a user tries to pick up one of cards.\n\n"
    </string>
</resources>
